<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>hbowie.net</title>
    <link>https://hbowie.net/</link>
    <description>Stuff by Herb Bowie</description>
    <language>en</language>
	<item>
	  <link>https://apps.apple.com/us/app/notenik/id1465997984</link>>
	  <guid>https://hbowie.net/2021/07/19/notenik-6.7.0-released.html</guid>
	  <pubdate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
	  <description>
	  	<p>Added support for Mathjax; enhanced Table of Contents generation for a single Note; enhanced Table of Contents generation for an entire Collection. </p>

	  </description>
	</item>
	<item>
	  <link>https://apps.apple.com/us/app/notenik/id1465997984</link>>
	  <guid>https://hbowie.net/2021/07/14/notenik-6.6.0-released.html</guid>
	  <pubdate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
	  <description>
	  	<p>Added a new Markdown extension to generate a Table of Contents for an entire Collection; added another new Markdown extension to generate an Index for an entire Collection; added another new Markdown extensions to generate a Tags Outline; added a new command to Generate a Web Book from a Collection; updated the Notenik Knowledge Base to make use of all of these new features. </p>

	  </description>
	</item>
	<item>
	  <link>https://practopian.org/blog/hbowie/kindness-by-design.html</link>>
	  <guid>https://hbowie.net/2021/07/14/kindness-by-design.html</guid>
	  <pubdate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
	  <description>
	  	<p>Perhaps we might come around to thinking that economic kindness, instead of being something indulged in capriciously by bleeding-heart liberals who are occasionally feeling generous, should in fact be a regular practice that is designed into our societies.  <br />
</p>

	  </description>
	</item>
	<item>
	  <link>https://apps.apple.com/us/app/notenik/id1465997984</link>>
	  <guid>https://hbowie.net/2021/07/07/notenik-6.5.0-released.html</guid>
	  <pubdate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
	  <description>
	  	<p>Added an option to backup an entire Collection to a compressed Zip file; made improvements to Streamlined Reading, to focus only on Seq, Title and Body fields; expanded the custom URL help command to allow an ID to be included, to point to a specific Note to be initially displayed; added a What&apos;s New command beneath the Help menu to show the user the latest changes to the app. </p>

	  </description>
	</item>
	<item>
	  <link>https://apps.apple.com/us/app/notenik/id1465997984</link>>
	  <guid>https://hbowie.net/2021/07/02/notenik-6.4.0-released.html</guid>
	  <pubdate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
	  <description>
	  	<p>Markdown parser support for definition lists; new Collection pref for Streamlined Reading, increasing focus on Body content on the Display tab; new Display navigation elements added when using Streamlined Reading, especially useful when using Seq and Level fields and sorting by Seq; new Notenik Knowledge Base, available from the Help menu (replacing all prior Help documentation). </p>

	  </description>
	</item>
	<item>
	  <link>https://practopian.org/blog/hbowie/are-political-parties-doing-us-more-harm-than-good.html</link>>
	  <guid>https://hbowie.net/2021/06/26/are-political-parties-doing-us-more-harm-than-good.html</guid>
	  <pubdate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
	  <description>
	  	<p>I&apos;ve been making the case lately that the Republican Party is in decline, and needs to reinvent itself. But perhaps something even more radical is needed. For when we look at the current state of our two-party system in the US, nothing about it makes any sense. </p>

	  </description>
	</item>
	<item>
	  <link>https://apps.apple.com/us/app/notenik/id1465997984</link>>
	  <guid>https://hbowie.net/2021/06/09/notenik-6.3.0-released.html</guid>
	  <pubdate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
	  <description>
	  	<p>Updated the Work List field type to allow entries for &apos;Novel&apos; and &apos;Podcast&apos; (and to make it easier to enter using all lowercase letters); added a new field type of Level, to indicate the depth of a Note within the structure of a Collection; added a new command to renumber the Seq field based on sequence and Level; added a new command to generate tags that will mirror the outline structure implied by the combination of Seq and Level fields. </p>

	  </description>
	</item>
	<item>
	  <link>https://practopian.org/appreciation/and-when-i-die.html</link>>
	  <guid>https://hbowie.net/2021/06/03/and-when-i-die-by-laura-nyro.html</guid>
	  <pubdate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
	  <description>
	  	<p>As children, our thoughts about death are stuff of dreams and fairy tales. As adults we learn to suppress these thoughts because we are busy getting on with things. But as teenagers, in this transition between nursery rhymes and real life, we tend to approach this topic with a frankness and curiosity that can be somewhat startling. Laura Nyro wrote her song &quot;And When I Die&quot; at the age of 17, and her refreshing treatment of the subject shows none of the reverence or piety that we learn to adopt as adults. </p>

	  </description>
	</item>
	<item>
	  <link>https://practopian.org/blog/hbowie/have-our-political-parties-turned-into-cults.html</link>>
	  <guid>https://hbowie.net/2021/05/31/have-our-political-parties-turned-into-cults.html</guid>
	  <pubdate>Mon, 31 May 2021 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
	  <description>
	  	<p>I recently wrote a piece offering &quot;Some Hard-Won Wisdom Concerning Cults.&quot; And I&apos;ve written a couple of pieces recently questioning the direction of the current Republican Party. And so, today, I want to ask the question: should either, or both, of our political parties be considered cults? </p>

	  </description>
	</item>
	<item>
	  <link>https://practopian.org/blog/hbowie/some-hard-won-wisdom-concerning-cults.html</link>>
	  <guid>https://hbowie.net/2021/05/27/some-hard-won-wisdom-concerning-cults.html</guid>
	  <pubdate>Thu, 27 May 2021 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
	  <description>
	  	<p>As someone who once belonged to an organization later determined to be a cult, I can tell you that the warning signs are not always obvious. </p>

	  </description>
	</item>
  </channel>
</rss>
