<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>hbowie.net</title>
    <link>https://hbowie.net/</link>
    <description>Stuff by Herb Bowie</description>
    <language>en</language>
	<item>
	  <link>https://practopian.org/blog/hbowie/a-resumption-of-our-humanity.html</link>>
	  <guid>https://hbowie.net/2021/01/21/a-resumption-of-our-humanity.html</guid>
	  <pubdate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
	  <description>
	  	<p>Overall, taking the pieces of the inaugural ceremony all together, the entire gestalt for me was a feeling that our feelings and practices of humanity, after being put on hold for four years, could now be resumed. </p>

	  </description>
	</item>
	<item>
	  <link>https://apps.apple.com/us/app/notenik/id1465997984</link>>
	  <guid>https://hbowie.net/2021/01/19/notenik-5.4.0-released.html</guid>
	  <pubdate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
	  <description>
	  	<ul>
<li>Added Notenik Intro for New Users </li>
<li>Added support for Markdown Code Fencing </li>
<li>Added Markdown Spec access from Help Menu </li>
<li>Reworked Display Fonts Prefs updates to make them more intuitive </li>
<li>Adjusted the font weights in the What&apos;s New Display </li>
<li>Corrected the sharing of an entire Note in Markdown </li>
</ul>

	  </description>
	</item>
	<item>
	  <link>https://practopian.org/blog/hbowie/the-big-truth.html</link>>
	  <guid>https://hbowie.net/2021/01/17/the-big-truth.html</guid>
	  <pubdate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
	  <description>
	  	<p>And so, I&apos;m starting to wonder, if we want to end The Big Lie, what undisclosed pieces of truth do we need to bring out into the open in order to achieve a more spacious shared understanding of our common reality? In other words, what is The Big Truth that we have yet to acknowledge? </p>

	  </description>
	</item>
	<item>
	  <link>https://apps.apple.com/us/app/notenik/id1465997984</link>>
	  <guid>https://hbowie.net/2021/01/14/notenik-5.3.0-released.html</guid>
	  <pubdate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
	  <description>
	  	<ul>
<li>Code Refactoring for Generation of a Unique ID for each Note </li>
<li>Added a Convenience function to edit a Collection&apos;s template file </li>
<li>Added a regular refresh to today&apos;s date </li>
<li>Added a Folder Picker to the Nav Board </li>
<li>Added a What&apos;s New Display </li>
</ul>

	  </description>
	</item>
	<item>
	  <link>https://practopian.org/blog/hbowie/the-clown-coup.html</link>>
	  <guid>https://hbowie.net/2021/01/08/the-clown-coup.html</guid>
	  <pubdate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
	  <description>
	  	<p>So much of our public attention is devoted to posturing, puffoonery[1] and empty opinionizing that many of our citizens seem to have lost the ability to distinguish this sort of behavior from actions that have real-world consequences. </p>

	  </description>
	</item>
	<item>
	  <link>https://apps.apple.com/us/app/notenik/id1465997984</link>>
	  <guid>https://hbowie.net/2021/01/04/notenik-5.2.0-released.html</guid>
	  <pubdate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
	  <description>
	  	<ul>
<li>Fixed an Import bug </li>
<li>Added options to Import data from OmniFocus </li>
<li>Added ability to Publish to Medium </li>
</ul>

	  </description>
	</item>
	<item>
	  <link>https://practopian.org/blog/hbowie/life-is-complicated.html</link>>
	  <guid>https://hbowie.net/2020/12/26/life-is-complicated.html</guid>
	  <pubdate>Sat, 26 Dec 2020 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
	  <description>
	  	<p>We all would like a quick fix of simple certainty, and no matter where we turn today, we can find an army of pushers waiting to feed our habit, even giving the stuff away for free, just to keep us hooked. </p>

	  </description>
	</item>
	<item>
	  <link>https://apps.apple.com/us/app/notenik/id1465997984</link>>
	  <guid>https://hbowie.net/2020/12/26/notenik-5.1.0-released.html</guid>
	  <pubdate>Sat, 26 Dec 2020 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
	  <description>
	  	<ul>
<li>Added Display Prefs Button to Update CSS </li>
<li>Added an Optional Date Modified Field </li>
<li>Changed the Author Sort to sort by first name first </li>
<li>Sorted out problems with following links, including application URLs </li>
<li>Added a function to close all completed tasks </li>
</ul>

	  </description>
	</item>
	<item>
	  <link>https://notenik.net/blog.html</link>>
	  <guid>https://hbowie.net/2020/12/10/notenik-turns-the-big-five-o.html</guid>
	  <pubdate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
	  <description>
	  	<p>Yes, that&apos;s right – Notenik version 5.0.0 has just been released, in all likelihood closing the books on 2020. So this feels like a good time to take a breather and look back on the path we&apos;ve traveled, along with new routes yet to explore. </p>

	  </description>
	</item>
	<item>
	  <link>https://apps.apple.com/us/app/notenik/id1465997984</link>>
	  <guid>https://hbowie.net/2020/11/30/notenik-4.9.0-released.html</guid>
	  <pubdate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
	  <description>
	  	<ul>
<li>Added a new File command to create a New Collection in iCloud </li>
<li>Added a new Transform command to Stash Notes in a subfolder </li>
<li>Added a new File command to Move a Collection to a new location </li>
<li>Added general support for a Web Collection, which has its Notes stored in a subfolder named notes </li>
<li>Added a Transform command to Browse a Web Index </li>
</ul>

	  </description>
	</item>
  </channel>
</rss>
