<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>hbowie.net</title>
<link>https://hbowie.net/</link>
<description>Stuff by Herb Bowie</description>
<language>en</language>
<item>
<link>https://apps.apple.com/us/app/notenik/id1465997984?mt=12</link>>
<guid>https://hbowie.net/2019/11/08/notenik-1.8.0-released.html</guid>
<pubdate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
<description>
<p>See <a href="https://notenik.net/swift.html#version-history">Notenik.net</a> for details.</p>

</description>
</item>
<item>
<link>https://practopian.org/blog/hbowie/the-personal-vs-the-institutional.html</link>>
<guid>https://hbowie.net/2019/11/01/the-personal-vs-the-institutional.html</guid>
<pubdate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
<description>
<p>Published on The Practical Utopian, and on Medium, and emailed to subscribers in The Practopian Perspective Issue 40.</p>

</description>
</item>
<item>
<link>https://rs500.blog/index.html</link>>
<guid>https://hbowie.net/2019/10/22/blogging-the-500-greatest-albums-of-all-time.html</guid>
<pubdate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
<description>
<p>A couple of friends/relatives of mine are taking a trip through Rolling Stone's list of the top 500 albums of all time, and commenting on each as we work our way up the list, starting with #500. We represent three different generations of listeners, and each brings his own unique perspective to this fascinating musical journey. See how far we've gotten and follow along. You might even discover some new old music worth a listen or two!</p>

</description>
</item>
<item>
<link>https://apps.apple.com/us/app/notenik/id1465997984?mt=12</link>>
<guid>https://hbowie.net/2019/10/15/notenik-1.6.0-released.html</guid>
<pubdate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
<description>
<p>Implemented a few additional fixes and minor enhancements. Changed scripted sorting so that fields whose labels begin with &quot;seq&quot; will be treated as sequence fields, meaning that numbers will sort in numeric sequence. Added a basic Textile parser that, while far from complete, is good enough for my needs, since I still use Textile on ReasonToRock.com.</p>

</description>
</item>
<item>
<link>https://apps.apple.com/us/app/notenik/id1465997984?mt=12</link>>
<guid>https://hbowie.net/2019/09/20/notenik-1.5.0-released.html</guid>
<pubdate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
<description>
<p>This release includes the following changes:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Enhanced logic for incrementing the Seq field;</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Added a dash/minus sign as a new variable modifier that can be used after the letter 'o' to trim the opening and closing paragraph tags from the HTML generated from the Markdown source;</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Added special treatment forr the Artist field, to allow it to be used in place of Author when sorting by Author;</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Added an option to the Template file to allow a long text field to be specified by placing '&lt;longtext&gt;' as the value for for a field specified in the template file;</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Additional refinements, including fixing a bug that sometimes ignored some variants of a newline character sequence when loading a Note from disk.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>See <a href="https://notenik.net">Notenik.net</a> for the updated User Guide and other documentation.</p>

</description>
</item>
<item>
<link>https://practopian.org/perspective/vol-1-issue-38-rejiggering-our-religion.html</link>>
<guid>https://hbowie.net/2019/09/16/practopian-perspective-issue-38-published.html</guid>
<pubdate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
<description>
<p>&quot;Rejiggering Our Religion&quot; published via email in The Practopian Perspective.</p>

</description>
</item>
<item>
<link>https://apps.apple.com/us/app/notenik/id1465997984?mt=12</link>>
<guid>https://hbowie.net/2019/09/09/notenik-1.4.1-released.html</guid>
<pubdate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
<description>
<p>This was a focused maintenance release designed to prevent the user from inadvertently specifying an existing folder as the repository for a new Notenik Collection.</p>

</description>
</item>
<item>
<link>https://apps.apple.com/us/app/notenik/id1465997984?mt=12</link>>
<guid>https://hbowie.net/2019/09/06/notenik-1.4.0-released.html</guid>
<pubdate>Fri, 06 Sep 2019 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
<description>
<p>This release includes the following changes:</p>
<ul>
<li>Improved the performance of Notenik when loading a new Collection (especially a large one);</li>
<li>The Work Type field now provides a drop-down menu from which an appropriate choice can be made;</li>
<li>A few minor bug fixes and improvements;</li>
<li>Recording of PSTextMerge/TDF Czar style scripts.</li>
</ul>
<p>See the latest version of the User Guide on <a href="https://notenik.net/swift.html">Notenik.net</a>.</p>

</description>
</item>
<item>
<link>https://hbowie.net/2019/08/26/elizabeth-warren-in-seattle.html</link>
<guid>https://hbowie.net/2019/08/26/elizabeth-warren-in-seattle.html</guid>
<pubdate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
<description>
<p>I was one of the 15,000 people who gathered under the Space Needle yesterday to hear Warren speak. There were several things about her that impressed me.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>She emphasized the need for structural change, starting with getting big money out of politics. This just makes so much sense because, without it, we'll soon be right back where we are now.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>She talked about the need for a wealth tax. This really clicked for me yesterday for the first time. I got it. People don't like income tax, because everyone has income, and no one wants to lose any of it to taxation. On the other hand, not everyone has wealth — especially as Warren defines it, above $50 million. So it will be easier to get voters to accept a new wealth tax than increases in income tax.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>As part of her opening origin story, she talked a lot about her &quot;much older&quot; brothers. It wasn't until I was riding home on the bus afterwards that I realized how smart this was, because it makes her sound much younger than her 70 years.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>All in all, she seems like a smart policy person who genuinely has our country's best interests at heart. but also a smart campaigner.</p>

</description>
</item>
<item>
<link>https://apps.apple.com/us/app/notenik/id1465997984?mt=12</link>>
<guid>https://hbowie.net/2019/08/16/notenik-1.3.0-released.html</guid>
<pubdate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
<description>
<p>This release includes the following changes:</p>
<ul>
<li>One or more files can now be attached to each Note;</li>
<li>Tags Export Preferences added, to allow tailoring of which Notes are included in an export, and which tags are included on those Notes;</li>
<li>A few miscellaneous improvements;</li>
<li>Playback of PSTextMerge/TDF Czar style scripts.</li>
</ul>
<p>This last item is a big one. It means that the Notenik.net site is now entirely generated by this latest version of Notenik writtein in Swift.</p>
<p>See the latest version of the User Guide on <a href="https://notenik.net/swift.html">Notenik.net</a>.</p>

</description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
