<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>hbowie.net</title>
<link>https://hbowie.net/</link>
<description>Stuff by Herb Bowie</description>
<language>en</language>
<item>
<link>https://rs500.blog</link>>
<guid>https://hbowie.net/2019/12/16/blogging-further-down-the-list-of-the-rolling-stone-top-500-albums.html</guid>
<pubdate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
<description>
<p>Some of the albums in the latest batch flew like eagles, while others sank like stones. Check out our latest multi-generational assessments of the top 500 albums of all time.</p>

</description>
</item>
<item>
<link>https://notenik.net</link>>
<guid>https://hbowie.net/2019/12/09/notenik-forges-ahead.html</guid>
<pubdate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
<description>
<p>I've been releasing new and improved versions of Notenik fairly regularly over the last couple of months, and it's now up to 2.2.0 in the Mac App Store, with 2.3.0 on the way.</p>
<p>As I write this, my little app now has 7 ratings in the store, and an average rating of 4.9.</p>
<p>I've received emails about the app from a couple of people I've never met before — one user in Australia, and another in Finland! Nice to know that my software can be used around the globe.</p>
<p>Brett Terpstra was nice enough to mention my app in one of his <a href="https://brettterpstra.com/2019/11/27/web-excursions-for-november-27-2019/">recent blog posts</a>, calling it &quot;intriguing.&quot;</p>
<p>But there's still more to do, and continuing work on Notenik keeps me busy doing something I enjoy.</p>
<p>If you have a Mac, and haven't yet checked it out, then I encourage you to give it a whirl!</p>

</description>
</item>
<item>
<link>https://apps.apple.com/us/app/notenik/id1465997984?mt=12</link>>
<guid>https://hbowie.net/2019/11/08/notenik-1.8.0-released.html</guid>
<pubdate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
<description>
<p>See <a href="https://notenik.net/swift.html#version-history">Notenik.net</a> for details.</p>

</description>
</item>
<item>
<link>https://practopian.org/blog/hbowie/the-personal-vs-the-institutional.html</link>>
<guid>https://hbowie.net/2019/11/01/the-personal-vs-the-institutional.html</guid>
<pubdate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
<description>
<p>Published on The Practical Utopian, and on Medium, and emailed to subscribers in The Practopian Perspective Issue 40.</p>

</description>
</item>
<item>
<link>https://rs500.blog/index.html</link>>
<guid>https://hbowie.net/2019/10/22/blogging-the-500-greatest-albums-of-all-time.html</guid>
<pubdate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
<description>
<p>A couple of friends/relatives of mine are taking a trip through Rolling Stone's list of the top 500 albums of all time, and commenting on each as we work our way up the list, starting with #500. We represent three different generations of listeners, and each brings his own unique perspective to this fascinating musical journey. See how far we've gotten and follow along. You might even discover some new old music worth a listen or two!</p>

</description>
</item>
<item>
<link>https://apps.apple.com/us/app/notenik/id1465997984?mt=12</link>>
<guid>https://hbowie.net/2019/10/15/notenik-1.6.0-released.html</guid>
<pubdate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
<description>
<p>Implemented a few additional fixes and minor enhancements. Changed scripted sorting so that fields whose labels begin with &quot;seq&quot; will be treated as sequence fields, meaning that numbers will sort in numeric sequence. Added a basic Textile parser that, while far from complete, is good enough for my needs, since I still use Textile on ReasonToRock.com.</p>

</description>
</item>
<item>
<link>https://apps.apple.com/us/app/notenik/id1465997984?mt=12</link>>
<guid>https://hbowie.net/2019/09/20/notenik-1.5.0-released.html</guid>
<pubdate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
<description>
<p>This release includes the following changes:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Enhanced logic for incrementing the Seq field;</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Added a dash/minus sign as a new variable modifier that can be used after the letter 'o' to trim the opening and closing paragraph tags from the HTML generated from the Markdown source;</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Added special treatment forr the Artist field, to allow it to be used in place of Author when sorting by Author;</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Added an option to the Template file to allow a long text field to be specified by placing '&lt;longtext&gt;' as the value for for a field specified in the template file;</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Additional refinements, including fixing a bug that sometimes ignored some variants of a newline character sequence when loading a Note from disk.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>See <a href="https://notenik.net">Notenik.net</a> for the updated User Guide and other documentation.</p>

</description>
</item>
<item>
<link>https://practopian.org/perspective/vol-1-issue-38-rejiggering-our-religion.html</link>>
<guid>https://hbowie.net/2019/09/16/practopian-perspective-issue-38-published.html</guid>
<pubdate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
<description>
<p>&quot;Rejiggering Our Religion&quot; published via email in The Practopian Perspective.</p>

</description>
</item>
<item>
<link>https://apps.apple.com/us/app/notenik/id1465997984?mt=12</link>>
<guid>https://hbowie.net/2019/09/09/notenik-1.4.1-released.html</guid>
<pubdate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
<description>
<p>This was a focused maintenance release designed to prevent the user from inadvertently specifying an existing folder as the repository for a new Notenik Collection.</p>

</description>
</item>
<item>
<link>https://apps.apple.com/us/app/notenik/id1465997984?mt=12</link>>
<guid>https://hbowie.net/2019/09/06/notenik-1.4.0-released.html</guid>
<pubdate>Fri, 06 Sep 2019 09:00:00 -0700</pubdate>
<description>
<p>This release includes the following changes:</p>
<ul>
<li>Improved the performance of Notenik when loading a new Collection (especially a large one);</li>
<li>The Work Type field now provides a drop-down menu from which an appropriate choice can be made;</li>
<li>A few minor bug fixes and improvements;</li>
<li>Recording of PSTextMerge/TDF Czar style scripts.</li>
</ul>
<p>See the latest version of the User Guide on <a href="https://notenik.net/swift.html">Notenik.net</a>.</p>

</description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
